Name :- Ishant Asija Contact No. :- 8607065188

E-mail Id : - iaishant40@gmail.com

Objective

To be associated with an organization that gives me a scope to enhance my knowledge and skills in accordance with the trends and be part of a team that dynamically works towards the growth of the organization and helps me to gain enriching experience.

Professional Qualification

Level	Institute/Board	Percentage	Year of Passing
CA-IPCC-II Group	ICAI	53%	May -2014
CA-IPCC-I Group	ICAI	67.5%	November -2013
CA-CPT	ICAI	80.5%	December -2012

Educational Qualification

Passed B.com from IGNOU with 61% in 2019.

Passed XIIth from CBSE with 89,2% in March'12.

Passed Xth from Haryana Board with 86.8% in March'10.

Articleship

RAM SHARMA & COMPANY

(From October 2013 to October 2016)

Articleship Work Experience

During Articleship, I have worked mainly in Statutory Audit, Tax Audit & ROC Work. Under statutory audit, covered the areas like Finalisation of Balance Sheet, Consolidation of Companies, accounting standards compliances, sales & purchase analysis, CARO, variance analysis, statutory dues, payroll, bank, fixed deposit, expenses etc. Under Tax audit, filling the form 3CD.

Assignment handled during Articleship period: -

S. No.	Client Name	Sector	Assignment
1.	The Fatehabad Central Dist. Co- op Bank Ltd.	Bank	Central Statutory Audit
2.	Canara Bank	Bank	Statutory Audit
3.	United Bank of India	Bank	Revenue Audit
4.	Sinhmar Securities Ltd.	Service Providing Company to event Like IPL	Statutory Audit & Tax Audit
5.	Company Formation	Various Company	ROC under MCA – 21

Experience

Total experience more than 7 years (including Articleship period).

- Regain Lab (24-Oct-2016 to 07-Jan-2019) as Accountant.
- Goodwill Hybrid Seeds (08-Jan-2019 till now) as Accounts Officer.

Work handled: -

- Maintaining Company accounts.
- Finalisation of Balance Sheet.
- GST Returns, TDS returns & MCA related regulations.
- Data Analysis.
- Graphical presentation of data with help of Excel.
- Sales data analysis.

Achievements

Cleared CA-CPT with distinction.

Technical Skills

Well versed with MS-Excel, MS-Word. Efficient with Tally, Marg ERP, Clear Tax Completed 100 Hours of ITT training from ICAI. Done GMCS-1.

Personal Details

Address : H.No. 780, VPO- Parbhuwala, Dist,. Hisar- 125113

Date of birth : March 13, 1994 Father's name : Mr. Jaswant Asija

Nationality : Indian
Marital Status : Unmarried

Languages known : English, Hindi, Punjabi